http://rd.tpage.com/?privacy

HOME
>> PRIVACY POLICY updated on November 18, 2002
Privacy Policy
Tpage.com considers and respects an individual's privacy seriously and importantly. The fundamental purpose of the services that Tpage provides you; for example, Offerboard enabling exchanges of trade leads, offers and inquiries, listing through the Tpage Company Directory, Tpage Showroom, and search engines, etc., requires that we gather, process, use and distribute the member's information which also you provide directly; for example, your company name, contact information, and homepage, etc. Therefore, Tpage.com does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. If you wish to remove your company or update your company's information, please Contact Us.
Information Collection and Use
As registering for the services provided on our website, you would be required to provide valid information including your name, company name, address, contact numbers and further personal information. We will use this information in providing services that you request, and letting you know of available services that give values to you and fit your business. We may also use this information to customize the contents for your convenience in using our website.
Furthermore, Tpage.com estimates and collects statistical Data about Tpage sites and users, such as IP address, browsers, pages viewed, and number of users etc. However, as doing so Tpage may not grant any individual name, email address or any other information related to the privacy concern to any users. We can use this data for improvement of Tpage content quality upon customer or market tendency, behavior, and trends. We may provide this statistical information to third parties without any exposure of private personal information and any notice to the provider.
Registration
In order to become a member at Tpage.com, an applicant must firstly complete the registration form with honesty and sincerity. While registering, the applicant is required to give their current and valid contact information, along with their company's profile. This information will be exposed on Tpage Company Directory and more relevant services at Tpage.com exclusively for the benefits of his/her trade business and for enhancing Tpage contents. Tpage.com does reserve the rights to use the company information provided by our users and any other information resulted posting at Tpage, into any form that Tpage.com sees it fits in. It is optional for a user to provide demographic information (such as gender, title and country).
All the user information shall be provided to banking merchants to enable transactions to take place and to allow us to determine the credit-worthiness of our users.
Partnerships & Relationships in Affiliation
We have established relationships or partnerships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services that Tpage may not contain. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our website, or through banners and letter mails in which both ourselves and these other parties (or partners) share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. The Privacy Policy of such other parties may differ from ours. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding of any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.
Cookies
Like most websites, Tpage uses cookies to store a member's profile. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the User. Usage of a cookie is taken place in no way linked to any personal private information while logging in our site. Once the member closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If the user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site, but access to some functions can be denied. Tpage does not use cookies to track a member's Internet viewing habits or for marketing purposes.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to obtain metrics, analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. In addition, your trade leads and contact information will be available to trade lead search engines from other web sites. Please be aware that Tpage is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the Privacy Policy of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. We employ all the latest technology in firewalls and the servers that we store our information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage at a hosting company. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to webmaster@tpage.com or simply Contact Us
Correcting Your Information
You can access the information that we collect online and maintain through normal updating methods. To update, correct or delete this information, you can go to My Info.
Site and Service Updates
We periodically send announcement on site and service to Members. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about upgrades and changes to service. We communicate with the members to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.
Users of our site will be informed when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this in purpose that our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will update this posting so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Therefore, you should check up on this Privacy Policy regularly.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact at :
Hanshin IT Tower 4F #408, Guro-dong 235, Guro-gu, Seoul, 152-050 Korea
Tel. +82-2-2108-7183
(Office Hour G.M.T 0:00(midnight) ~ 9:00 A.M)
Fax
+82-2-2108-7178
E-mail : webmaster@tpage.com
[If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted Privacy Policy, you should Contact Us. ]
